<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Email on Index</title>
    <link>https://imlauerjobs.github.io/@email/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Email on Index</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>es-ar</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 04:33:22 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://imlauerjobs.github.io/@email/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Domain Transfer Email migration Google Drive Cleanup</title>
      <link>https://imlauerjobs.github.io/domain_transfer_email_migration_google_drive_cleanup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 04:33:22 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imlauerjobs.github.io/domain_transfer_email_migration_google_drive_cleanup/</guid>
      <description>I have a web domain currently hosted by Google and I&amp;rsquo;m looking to transfer it to a private hosting service. As part of this process, I need assistance with migrating all email messages to ensure no data is lost.&#xA;Additionally, I need help reviewing my Google Drive to delete unnecessary files, organize the needed data into folders, and save it securely to my computer.&#xA;The ideal candidate will have experience with Google Workspace, including Gmail and Google Drive, and should be skilled in email migration, domain transfers, and data organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email_Server_Setup_for_Password_Reset_Solutions</title>
      <link>https://imlauerjobs.github.io/email_server_setup_for_password_reset_solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 21:08:23 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imlauerjobs.github.io/email_server_setup_for_password_reset_solutions/</guid>
      <description>Buscamos un profesional independiente capacitado para configurar un servidor de correo electrónico confiable diseñado específicamente para soluciones de restablecimiento de contraseña. El candidato ideal tendrá experiencia en la configuración de servidores de correo electrónico para garantizar procesos de recuperación de contraseñas seguros y eficientes. Será responsable de implementar las mejores prácticas para la seguridad y la capacidad de entrega del correo electrónico, así como de solucionar cualquier problema que surja durante la configuración.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
